National Council of Jewish Women Collection 0009.003.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Series V: Hartford Section/Financial_Fundraising/B
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Artists-in-Residences -- Planning, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Artists-in-Residences -- Publicity, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Artists-in-Residences -- Sales, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Auctionata, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Bargainata, undated
- Series VI: Hartford Section/Fundraising/Concerts-Meeting Programs
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/"Urbanities: 1955" Musical Comedy
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/85th anniversary, 1995, 1955
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Concerts, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Concerts -- Hartford Symphony, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Stock Certificates, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Tag Sales, undated
  - Hartford Section/Fundraising/Thrift Shop, undated
  - Hartford Section/Grants/Pantry Grant, undated
  - Hartford Section/Historical Highlights, undated
  - Hartford Section/Historical Research Notes -- Miscellaneous, undated
  - Hartford Section/Historical Research Notes -- Scholarship Funds, undated
  - Hartford Section/Historical Research Notes – Thesis by Rachel Holtzberg on Role of NCJW in Immigrant Aid, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1920s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1940s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1950s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1960s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1970s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1980s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 1990s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Meeting Programs, 2000s, undated
- Series VII: Hartford Section/Members- Miscellaneous
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Administrative Records, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Individual Members, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Committee Reports, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1940s to 1950s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1955 to 1957, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1960s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1970s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1970s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1980s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Membership Rosters, 1990s, undated
  - Hartford Section/Members and Membership/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Hartford Section/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Life Members, undated
- Series VIII: Hartford Section/Newsletters 1930-1979
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1930 to 1938, 1930-1938
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1939 to 1940, 1939-1940
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1941 to 1944, 1941-1944
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1945 to 1950, 1945-1950
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1951 to 1959, 1951-1959
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1960 to 1969, 1960-1969
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1970 to 1975, 1970-1975
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1976 to 1977, 1976-1977
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1978 to 1979, 1978-1979
- Series IX: Hartford Section/Newsletters 1980-2000s
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1980 to 1982, 1980-1982
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1983
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1984 to 1985, 1984-1985
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1986 to 1988, 1986-1988
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1989 to 1992, 1989-1992
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1993 to 1997, 1993-1997
  - Hartford Section/Newsletter, 1998 to 2000s, 1998-2000
- Series X: Hartford Section/Newspaper Clippings --Service Projects A-L
  - Hartford Section/Newspaper clippings, undated
  - Hartford Section/Publicity, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Automobile emergency banner, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Blind Adults, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Chanukah Baskets, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Child Care, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Civil Liberties and Civil Rights, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Close Harmony Week, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Contemporary Jewish Affairs & Israeli Affairs, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Day of the Working Parent, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Day of the Working Parent -- Lunchbox contents, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Domestic Violence, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Girl Scout Troop #38, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Greater Hartford Shalom, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Hartford Shalom, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Hebrew University Education Programs, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Immigrants -- Early 20th Century, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Immigrants -- Soviet Jewry, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Immigrants -- Soviet Jewry, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Immigrants -- WWII Refugees, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Inflation Coalition, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Interfaith Activities, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Interval House (House Pins), undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Justice for Children Coalition, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Justice for Children Coalition, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Legislative Monitoring, undated
- Series XI: Hartford Section/Service Projects M-Z-Hartford Section/Skits
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Meals-on-Wheels, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Milk and Health Station, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Million Mom March (gun control), undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/North End Pre-School, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Religious School, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Road Shows, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Scholarship Funds, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/School for Community Action, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Senior Adult Programs, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Ship-a-Box Project, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Soup Kitchens, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/STOP, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/Take Time to Care, undated
  - Hartford Section/Service Projects/World War II Projects, undated
  - Hartford Section/Shalom Book, undated
  - Hartford Section/Skits, undated
  - Hartford Section/SPA Committee, undated
  - Hartford Section/Women who dare calendar, 1998-1999
  - Hartford Section/Woman of the Year/Marsha Lotstein, 1998, undated
- Series XII: National Organization: Anniversaries - M
  - National Organization/Anniversaries/100th Anniversary of National Organization, 1993
  - National Organization/Anniversaries/100th Anniversary of National Organization, 1993
  - National Organization/Board of Directors/Policies, undated
  - National Organization/Brochures, undated
  - National Organization/Conferences/10th Triennial Convention, 1923
  - National Organization/Conferences/11th and 16th Triennial Conventions, 1926 and 1940, 1926-1940
  - National Organization/Conferences/39th Triennial Convention, 1993 (100th Anniversary)
  - National Organization/Conferences/7th and 8th Triennial Conventions, 1914 and 1917, 1914-1917
  - National Organization/Conferences/9th Triennial Convention, 1920
  - National Organization/Conferences/National Day of the Working Parent, 1993
  - National Organization/Conferences/40th National Convention (1996)
- Series XIII: National Organization: Conferences - M
  - National Organization/Conferences/41st National Convention (1999)
  - National Organization/Conferences/42nd National Convention (2002)
  - National Organization/Conferences/Leadership Conference 1999-2003
  - National Organization/Conferences/Washington Institute, 1995, 1998
  - National Organization/Conferences/Washington Institute, 2001, 2004
  - National Organization/Constitution and By-Laws, undated
  - National Organization/Convention 35th, 1983
  - National Organization/Department of Farm and Rural Work, undated
  - National Organization/Miscellaneous, undated
- Series XIV: Publicity and Newsletters
  - National Organization/Newsletters–National Organization/Z, undated
  - Northeastern District, undated
  - Spare copies of anniversary program and cover, undated
  - National Organization/Newsletters "Council Woman", undated
  - National Organization/Newsletters "Insight", undated
  - National Organization/Newsletters "Jewish Woman" (1927), undated
  - National Organization/Newsletters "NCJW Journal", undated
  - National Organization/Pennant, undated
  - National Organization/Publicity, undated
  - National Organization/Publicity, undated
  - National Organization/Religious Materials, undated
  - National Organization/Training Materials, undated
  - Northeastern District, undated
  - Northeastern District/Convention in Hartford, 1978
  - National Organization /Greater Hartford Section/100th Anniversary, undated
  - Spare copies of anniversary program and cover, undated
- Series XV: Photographs
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Anniversaries, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Awards and Honors/Woman of the Year, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Awards and Honors received, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Conferences and Conventions, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Miscellaneous, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Programs, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Service Projects, undated
  - National Council of Jewish Women/Hartford Section/Washington Institute/with Christopher Dodd, 2001, undated
- Series XVI: Scrapbooks
  - Hartford Section 75th Anniversary, 1985
  - Hartford Section 75th Anniversary/guest book, 1985
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1950s (loose-leaf)
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1964-1970, mostly Evening Branch
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1966-1968
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings, Flyers, and Photographs, 1970-1975
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings, Flyers, and Photographs, 1975-1978
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1975-1979
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1977-1984
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1980-1982
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1982-1983
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings and Flyers, 1983-1990
- Series XVII: Artifacts
  - Commemorative metal badges, Soviet Jewry and women's issues, undated
  - 11th Triennial Convention Pin (1926) of Celia K. Levy (Mrs. H.P. Levy), founder and honorary president of the Hartford Section, undated
  - Convention pennants and memorabilia, undated
  - Ribbons signifying achievement of national support quota, undated
  - Automobile emergency banner, see also Hartford Chapter, undated
  - Section membership award paperweight, undated
  - Membership drive stickers, undated
  - Day of the Working Parent lunchbox, undated
  - Printed napkins, undated
  - Dice, undated
  - NCJW paperclip, undated
  - Life membership Achievement Award flag, undated
  - Wipe-off weekly magnetic planner, undated
  - Plaques from Jewish Family Service (1978-79), the Governor's Council on Voluntary, 1978-1979
  - Action (1987) and Jewish Federation for Russian Resettlement work (1979), 1979-1987